resumegenius.com 2017-04-26

# Users Privacy Policy | Resume Genius

### ResumeGenius.com

Version Date: May 2, 2012

## GENERAL

ResumeGenius.com (“Company” or “we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of its users (“user” or “you”) that utilize our resume and cover letter creation and distribution features and services (the “Website Services”) which are accessible through www.ResumeGenius.com, co-branded and private label subdomains, and through other Internet locations, including via other media forms and media channels related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Website”). The following Company privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you, as a user of the Website Services, about the types of information that Company may gather about or collect from you in connection with your use of the Website Services. It also is intended to explain the conditions under which Company uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Changes to this Privacy Policy are discussed at the end of this document. Each time you use the Website Services, however, the current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time you use the Website Services you should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the beginning of this document) and review any changes since the last time you used the Website Services.

Our Website is hosted in the United States of America and is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you are accessing our Website from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your personal information to us in the United States, and by using our Website, you consent to that transfer and use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You also agree to abide by the applicable laws of applicable states and U.S. federal law concerning your use of the Website and your agreements with us. Any persons accessing our Website from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing the use of the Internet, including personal data collection, use and disclosure different from those of the jurisdictions mentioned above may only use the Website in a manner lawful in their jurisdiction. If your use of our Website would be unlawful in your jurisdiction, please do not use the Website.

BY USING OR ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

## CHILDREN

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides personal information through the Website represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that personal information has been collected from a user under 13 years of age on or through the Website, then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has transferred personal information to the Website, please contact Company using our contact information below to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

## COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

### Website Registration

“Personally-Identifying Information” is information such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person. Company collects certain Personally-Identifying Information from and about Website users. Much of the Personally-Identifying Information collected by Company about users is information provided by users themselves at the time they create an account. That information may include each user’s name, address, and email address. We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender, job title, age, date of birth, username, hometown, country, postal code and other demographic information, and other relevant information as determined by Company from time to time. If you are transacting business with us, then we may also collect credit or debit card information or other payment information. Users of the Website are under no obligation to provide Company with Personally-Identifying Information of any kind, with the caveat that a user’s refusal to do so may prevent the user from using certain Website features.

BY REGISTERING WITH OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS “COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION” SECTION.

### Company Communications

We may occasionally use names and email addresses and other contact information provided to us to send users notifications regarding new services offered by the Website that we think they may find valuable. We may also send users service-related announcements from time to time that may include, without limitation, notifications of service expiration and renewal and related payment information, as well as other information related to the expiration or renewal. We reserve the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

### Company Disclosures

Company will disclose Personally-Identifying Information under the following circumstances:

  * **By Law or to Protect Rights.**  When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our Company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements or policies, in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
  * **Potential Employers and Related Businesses**  We may allow potential employers, employment agencies, and other businesses involved in personnel placement and related services to access the resume that you have created and maintain on the Website. These businesses may contact you regarding potential employment using any contact information that appears on your resume. You may opt-out of this service through your account settings or by contacting Company using the contact information set forth below. As soon as practical after you opt-out, Company will no longer provide access to your resume to these businesses. However, such businesses that have already accessed your resume prior to such date may still contact you, and you will need to notify such businesses directly if you do not want them to continue contacting you.
  * **Direct Mail Partners.**  From time to time we may share our postal mailing list with selected providers of goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive mailings from these providers, you may opt-out at the time you register for our Website, or at any time thereafter by going to your account settings or contacting us using the contact information below.
  * **Marketing Communications.**  Unless users opt-out from receiving Company marketing materials upon registration, Company will email users about products and services that Company believes may be of interest to them and Company also will provide users’ email information to third parties, so that those third parties may directly contact users about additional products and services. If a user wishes to opt-out of receiving marketing materials from Company, user may do so by following the unsubscribe link in email communications, by going to your account settings or contacting us using the contact information below. Similarly, to cease having your email information provided to third parties, you may do so by going to your account settings or contacting us using the contact information below. Even after opting-out, a user may continue to receive marketing emails from third parties to whom Company already has provided the user’s email information. Users will be responsible for directly contacting such third parties to request cessation of further marketing emails.
  * **Business Partners:**  When you make purchases or engage in promotions offered through our Website or our services, we may share Personally-Identifying Information with the businesses with which we partner to offer you those products, services, promotions, contests and/or sweepstakes. When you elect to engage in a particular merchant’s offer or program, you authorize us to provide your email address and other information to that merchant.
  * **Co-Branded Partners.**  If you have joined our Website through one of our co-branded websites, then we may also share your Personally-Identifying Information with the co-branded partner that is associated with the co-branded website. Such shared information will be subject to the privacy policies applicable to such co-branded partner.
  * **Affiliates.**  We may share some or all of your personal information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates would include a parent company or any subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that we control or that is under common control with us.
  * **Third Party Service Providers.**  We may share your Personally-Identifying Information, which may include your name and contact information (including email address) with our authorized service providers that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality, and supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features offered through our Website. We may also share your name, contact information and credit card information with our authorized service providers who process credit card payments. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purpose.
  * **Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.**  Company reserves the right to transfer all Personally-Identifying Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Company’s assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally-Identifying Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and are given an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personally-Identifying Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the successor organization.

### Changing Personally-Identifying Information; Account Termination

You may at any time review or change your Personally-Identifying Information, or terminate your account, by visiting your account settings or by contacting us using the contact information below. Upon your request, we will deactivate or delete your account and contact information from our active databases. Such information will be deactivated or deleted as soon as practicable based on your account activity and accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. To make this request, contact us as provided below. We will retain in our files some personal information to prevent fraud, to troubleshoot problems, to assist with any investigations, to enforce our Terms of Use and to comply with legal requirements as is permitted by law.

### General Use

We use the Personally-Identifiable Information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Website to: deliver the products and services that you have requested, manage your account and provide you with customer support, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, customize your experience, detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our Terms of Use, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems. In particular, we may examine your Personally-Identifiable Information to identify users using multiple user IDs or aliases. We may compare and review your Personally-Identifiable Information for accuracy and to detect errors and omissions. We may use financial information or payment method to process payment for any purchases made on our Website, to protect against or identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.

## GATHERING, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF NON-PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

### Users of the Website Generally

“Non-Personally-Identifying Information” is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person. Like most website operators, Company gathers from users of the Website Non-Personally-Identifying Information of the sort that Web browsers, depending on their settings, may make available. That information includes the user’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type, and the locations of the Web pages the user views right before arriving at, while navigating and immediately after leaving the Website. Company analyzes Non-Personally-Identifying Information gathered from users of the Website to help Company better understand how the Website is being used. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Company is able to better design the Website to improve users’ experiences, both in terms of content and ease of use. From time to time, Company may also release the Non-Personally-Identifying Information gathered from Website users in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website.

### Web Cookies

A “Web Cookie” is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the site. Company uses Web Cookies to track the pages that users visit during each Website session, both to help Company improve users’ experiences and to help Company understand how the Website is being used. As with other Non-Personally-Identifying Information gathered from users of the Website, Company analyzes and discloses in aggregated form information gathered using Web Cookies, so as to help Company, its partners and others better understand how the Website is being used. Company does not attempt to link information gathered using Web Cookies to Personally-Identifying Information. However, when logged in, a Web Cookie is associated with a unique user profile. Therefore, users are advised to clear Web Cookies from computers whenever finished with a logged in session if those computers will also be used by other persons. PLEASE NOTE THAT IF YOU SET YOUR BROWSER TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU WILL NOT BE GRANTED ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE. WEBSITE USERS WHO REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

### Third Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to this and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third party ad servers’ and networks’ Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please follow the following link: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.

We allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements and we may use any of the non-personally identifiable attributes we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.

### Web Beacons

A “Web Beacon” is an object that is embedded in a web page that is usually invisible to the user and allows website operators to check whether a user has viewed a particular web page or an email. Company may use Web Beacons on the Website and in emails to count users who have visited particular pages, viewed emails, and to deliver co-branded services. Web Beacons are not used to access users’ Personally-Identifying Information; they are a technique Company may use to compile aggregated statistics about Website usage. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information including a Web Cookie number, time and date of a page or email view, and a description of the page or email on which the Web Beacon resides. You may not decline Web Beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all Web Cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a Web Cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline Web Cookies on an individual basis.

### Aggregated and Non-Personally-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated and Non-Personally Identifying Information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We may also share it with third parties and our affiliate companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Website and on websites of third parties. We may combine Non-Personally Identifying Information we collect with additional Non-Personally Identifying Information collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our Website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any Personally-Identifying Information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to target content and advertising.

## SURVEYS

From time to time, Company may ask Website users to participate in surveys designed to help Company improve the Website. Any Personally-Identifying Information provided to Company in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in non-personally-identifying, aggregated form.

## SECURITY

We take security of your Personally-Identifying Information seriously and use reasonable electronic, personnel, and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration, or misuse. However, please be advised that even the best security measures cannot fully eliminate all risks. We cannot control the actions of other users with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures.

The Website encrypts sensitive information such as your credit card number and your personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your computer to our servers. In addition, we use commercially reasonable efforts to limit access to your Personally-Identifying Information to the employees, agents, and officers of Company who need the information for their jobs. All of our employees are kept up to date on our privacy and security practices. For more information about the security measures Company uses in connection with the Website, please contact us using the contact information found below.

## PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

Company may, in its sole discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any and all changes to Company’s Privacy Policy will be reflected on this page and the date new versions are posted will be stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. Users should regularly check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Company will always post new versions of the Privacy Policy on the Website. However, Company may, as determined in its discretion, decide to notify users of changes made to this Privacy Policy via email or otherwise. Accordingly, it is important that users always maintain and update their contact information.

## CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to our privacy officer as listed below.

## CONTACT

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our privacy officer at:

U.S. Office:  
Resume Companion LLC  
427 N Tatnall St #95492  
Wilmington, DE 19801-2230  
United States

Europe Office:  
RGO Resume Technologies Ltd. dba ResumeGenius.com  
Karpenision, 9 Strovolos, 2021  
Nicosia, Cyprus

Contacting us:  
Email: support@resumegenius.com  
Phone: (866) 215-9048 (available Monday to Friday, 8AM – 12AM (Midnight) EDT)
